const quizData = [
    {
        "question": "What is the full name of Harry Potter's father?",
        "options": ["Henry James Potter", "James Sirius Potter", "James Potter", "Harry James Potter"],
        "correct": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "Which spell does Hermione use to fix Harry's broken wand in 'Harry Potter and the Deathly Hallows'?",
        "options": ["Reparo", "Episkey", "Rennervate", "Finite Incantatem"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the vault in Gringotts that contains the Philosopher's Stone?",
        "options": ["Vault 713", "Vault 394", "Vault 687", "Vault 777"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the headmaster of Hogwarts before Albus Dumbledore?",
        "options": ["Phineas Nigellus Black", "Armando Dippet", "Everard", "Dilys Derwent"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the core of Voldemort's wand?",
        "options": ["Phoenix feather", "Dragon heartstring", "Unicorn hair", "Thestral tail hair"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of the house-elf who serves the Black family?",
        "options": ["Kreacher", "Winky", "Dobby", "S.P.E.W."],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which potion allows the drinker to take on the appearance of someone else?",
        "options": ["Felix Felicis", "Polyjuice Potion", "Amortentia", "Veritaserum"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "Who was the master of the Elder Wand before Albus Dumbledore?",
        "options": ["Gellert Grindelwald", "Harry Potter", "Tom Riddle", "Gregorovitch"],
        "correct": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "Which spell did Severus Snape create to protect the students from the Dark Arts?",
        "options": ["Sectumsempra", "Protego", "Expelliarmus", "Legilimens"],
        "correct": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "In which magical creature’s blood is Harry’s ability to speak Parseltongue attributed?",
        "options": ["Basilisk", "Dragons", "Hippogriffs", "Phoenix"],
        "correct": 0
    }
];

export default quizData;